(Leonard:)How could you have a girlfriend?
(Leonard:)You can't even speak to women.
(Raj:)Two words-- deaf chick.
(Raj:)It doesn't matter
(Raj:)if I can't talk,
because she can't hear me.
(Leonard:)What?
(Raj:)That's what she said.
(Leonard:)Great. You have a girlfriend,
Howard's got a girlfriend,
(Leonard:)Sheldon's got
a girl...
No, no, no, no!
(Leonard:)...who's a friend.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Leonard:)What about you, Stuart?
(Leonard:)You have a
girlfriend yet?
(Stuart:)Oh, yeah. Yeah.
(Stuart:)I met her at Comic-Con,
the one place in the world
(Stuart:)where saying
"I own a comic bookstore"
(Stuart:)is an actual pickup line.
(Leonard:)Oh. Well, good for you.
(Stuart:)Not really. She's horrible.
(Stuart:)When she wants to have sex,
(Stuart:)she puts on her plus-size
Wonder Woman costume and shouts,
"Who wants to take a ride
in my invisible plane?"
(Leonard:)Why don't you just
break up with her?
(Stuart:)No, no, I can't.
(Leonard:)Why not?
'Cause then I'd be alone,
(Stuart:)like you.
(Raj:)Dude, why don't you just invoke
your girlfriend pact
(Raj:)with Wolowitz?